Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Spokane International Railway (Box 166, Folder 4)
- Spokane, Portland & Seattle (Box 166, Folder 5)
- Springfield and Southwest R.R. Co. (Box 166, Folder 6)
- Springfield Terminal Railway Company (Box 166, Folder 7)
- St. Johnsbury & Lake Champlain (Box 166, Folder 8)
- The St. Joseph & Grand Island Railway Co. (Box 166, Folder 9)
- St. Joseph & Grand Island (Box 166, Folder 10)
- St. Joseph Stock Yard (Box 166, Folder 11)
- St. Joseph Union Depot Company (Box 166, Folder 12)
- Southern Pacific (Pacific System) (Box 166, Folder 13)
- Southwest Missouri R.R. (Box 166, Folder 14)
- St. Louis Southwestern RY (Box 166, Folder 15)
- Booklets & Pamphlets (Box 166, Folder 16)
- St. Joseph Union Depot Company (Box 166, Folder 17)
- St. Louis & Hannibal Railroad (Box 166, Folder 18)
- St. Louis National Stock Yards (Box 166, Folder 19)
- St. Louis & North Arkansas (Box 166, Folder 20)
- St. Louis, Troy & Eastern Railroad (Box 166, Folder 21)
- St. Paul Union Depot Company (Box 166, Folder 22)
- State Belt Railroad (California) (Box 166, Folder 23)
- Staten Island Rapid Transit Railway (Box 166, Folder 24)
- Steelton and Highspire Railroad (Box 166, Folder 25)
- Sumpter Valley Railway Company (Box 166, Folder 26)
- Susquehanna & New York R.R. (Box 166, Folder 27)
- Southern Pacific (Atlantic System) (Box 166, Folder 28)
- St. Louis, San Francisco RY (Box 166, Folder 29)
- Sacramento Northern Railway (Box 166, Folder 30)
- Sydney & Louisburg Railway (Box 166, Folder 31)
- Agreement between Sydney & Louisburg Railway Co. & B.R.T. (Box 166, Folder 32)
- Temiscouata Railway (Box 166, Folder 33)
- Booklets & Pamphlets (Box 167, Folder 1)
- Temiskaming & Northern Ontario (Box 167, Folder 2)
- Texas & Pacific Railway (Box 167, Folder 3)
- Texas Central Railroad Company (Box 167, Folder 4)
- Texas Short Lines (Box 167, Folder 5)
- Thousand Islands Railway (Box 167, Folder 6)
- Toledo, St. Louis & Western (Box 167, Folder 7)
- Texas City Terminal Railway (Yard Schedule) (Box 167, Folder 8)
- Texas Mexican Railway Company (Box 167, Folder 9)
- Temiscouta Railway Company (Box 167, Folder 10)
- Texas- New Mexico Railway Company (Box 167, Folder 11)
- Texas Midland Railroad (Box 167, Folder 12)
- Tennessee Central Railway (Box 167, Folder 13)
- Tallulah Falls Railway (Box 167, Folder 14)
- Tennessee Central Railroad (Box 167, Folder 15)
- Tennessee Railroad Company (Box 167, Folder 16)
- Tennessee, Alabama & Georgia (Box 167, Folder 17)
- Texas and Northern Railway Company (Box 167, Folder 18)
- Texas & Pacific (Box 167, Folder 19)
- The Union Depot Company (Box 167, Folder 20)
- Union Depot Company (Columbus, Ohio) (Box 167, Folder 21)
- Union Belt of Detroit- (Box 167, Folder 22)
- Troy Iron Works (Republic Steel Co.) (Box 167, Folder 23)
- Trinity and Brazos Valley Ry. Co. (Box 167, Folder 24)
- Tremont & Gulf Railway Co. (Box 167, Folder 25)
- Toronto, Hamilton & Buffalo (Box 167, Folder 26)
- Tonopah & Tidewater Railroad (Box 167, Folder 27)
- Tonopah & Goldfield Railroad (Box 167, Folder 28)
- Toledo Terminal Railroad (Box 167, Folder 29)
- Toledo, Peoria & Western R.R. (Box 167, Folder 30)
- Terminal R.R. Association of St. Louis (Box 167, Folder 31)
- Unadilla Valley Railroad Co. (Box 167, Folder 32)
- Ulster & Delaware Railroad Company (Box 167, Folder 33)
- Union Railway Company (Memphis) (Box 167, Folder 34)
- The Union Terminal Co. (Dallas, Texas) (Box 167, Folder 35)
- Union Pacific Railroad (East) (Box 167, Folder 36)
- Booklets & Pamphlets (Box 168, Folder 1)
- Union Pacific (Northwest District) (Box 168, Folder 2)
- Union Pacific Railroad (S.C.D.) (Box 168, Folder 3)
- Union Railroad (Pittsburgh) (Box 168, Folder 4)
- Union Stock Yards Co. of Omaha (Box 168, Folder 5)
- Union Terminal Company (St. Joseph) (Box 168, Folder 6)
- Utah Railway (Box 168, Folder 7)
- Vancouver Harbour Board Terminal (Box 168, Folder 8)
- Vandalia Railroad Company (Box 168, Folder 9)
- Verde Tunnel and Smelter Railroad (Box 168, Folder 10)
- Verde Tunnel and Smelter RR. Co. (Box 168, Folder 11)
- Virginia & Southwestern (Box 168, Folder 12)
- Virginian Railroad (Box 168, Folder 13)
- Wabash Railroad (Box 168, Folder 14)
- Wabash-Pere Marquette (Joint Territory Detroit, Michigan) (Box 168, Folder 15)
- Washington, Baltimore & Annapolis (Electric - Ceased Operation 5-20-35) (Box 168, Folder 16)
- Washington County RR. (Now B&O) (Box 168, Folder 17)
- Washington Terminal Railway (Box 168, Folder 18)
- Western Allegheny RR. (Now PRR) (Box 168, Folder 19)
- Western Maryland Railroad (Box 168, Folder 20)
- Western Pacific Railway (Box 168, Folder 21)
- West Side Lumber Company (Narrow gauge-Tuolumne Co. Calif.) (Box 168, Folder 22)
- Wheeling & Lake Erie RR. (Box 168, Folder 23)
- Wheeling Terminal Ry. (Now PRR) (Box 168, Folder 24)
- White River Railroad (Kingan & Co) (Indianapolis) (Box 168, Folder 25)
- Wichita Falls & Southern RY (Box 168, Folder 26)
- Wichita Falls & Southern Railroad (Box 168, Folder 27)
- Wichita Terminal Association (Box 168, Folder 28)
- Wichita Valley Railroad (Now CB&Q) (Box 168, Folder 29)
- Winona Railroad (Box 168, Folder 30)
- Wisconsin & Michigan (Abandoned 1938) (Box 168, Folder 31)
- Wisconsin Central Ry. (Now Soo Line) (Box 168, Folder 32)
- Yakima Valley Transportation Co. (Box 168, Folder 33)
- Yazoo & Mississippi Valley RR. (Box 168, Folder 34)
- Yosemite Valley Railway (Box 168, Folder 35)
- Yosemite Valley Railway Company (Box 168, Folder 36)
- Zanesville & Western Ry. (NYC-OCL) (Box 168, Folder 37)
- 5446 BRT Conv. Program, 1909 (Box 168, Folder 38)
- Akron, Canton & Youngstown (Box 169, Folder 1)
- Adirondack Transit Lines (Box 169, Folder 2)
- Atchison, Topeka (Box 169, Folder 3)
- Atchison, Topeka (Box 169, Folder 4)
- Baltimore & Ohio (Box 169, Folder 5)
- Bingham & Garfield Railway Co. (Box 169, Folder 6)
- Carey Transportation (Box 169, Folder 7)
- Chesapeake & Ohio RR (Box 169, Folder 8)
- Chicago & Eastern Ill. (Box 169, Folder 9)
- Chicago, Burlington (Box 169, Folder 10)
- Chicago Great Western (Box 169, Folder 11)
- Chicago, Indianapolis (Box 169, Folder 12)
- Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul (Box 169, Folder 13)
- Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago (Box 169, Folder 14)
- Cleveland Union Terminal (Box 169, Folder 15)
- Cleveland Yard Territory (Box 169, Folder 16)
- Clinchfield RR Co. (Box 169, Folder 17)
- Colorado & Wyoming RR (Box 169, Folder 18)
- Cuyahoga Valley (Box 169, Folder 19)
- Delaware & Hudson System (Box 169, Folder 20)
- Delaware, Lackawanna & Western (Box 169, Folder 21)
- Detroit & Toledo (Box 169, Folder 22)
- Duluth, Missabe & Iron (Box 169, Folder 23)
- Eastern, Western, Southeastern (Box 169, Folder 24)
- Elgin, Joliet & Western (Box 169, Folder 25)
- Erie (Box 169, Folder 26)
- Florida East Coast RR (Box 169, Folder 27)
- Fort Worth & Denver (Box 169, Folder 28)
- Galveston Terminal (Box 169, Folder 29)
- Great Northern Pacific (Box 169, Folder 30)
- Greyhound (Box 169, Folder 31)
- Gulf, Colorado & Santa Fe (Box 169, Folder 32)
- Gulf, Mobile & Ohio (Box 169, Folder 33)
- Houston Belt & Terminal (Box 169, Folder 34)
- Hudson & Manhattan RR (Box 169, Folder 35)
- Illinois Central Ry. (Box 169, Folder 36)
- Inter-City Transportation Co. (Box 169, Folder 37)
- Int'l & Great Northern (Box 169, Folder 38)
- Kansas City Terminal (Box 169, Folder 39)
- Kennecott Copper Corp. (Box 169, Folder 40)
- Lehigh Valley (Box 169, Folder 41)
- Long Island RR (Box 169, Folder 42)
- Los Angeles Metropolitan. Transit (Box 169, Folder 43)
- Louisville & Nashville (Box 169, Folder 44)
- Metropolitan. Coach Lines (Box 170, Folder 1)
- Missouri, Kansas & Texas (Box 170, Folder 2)
- Monongahela (Box 170, Folder 3)
- Nashville, Chattanooga (Box 170, Folder 4)
- New Haven (Box 170, Folder 5)
- New York Central (Box 170, Folder 6)
- New York, Chicago & St. Louis (Box 170, Folder 7)
- NY, New Haven (Box 170, Folder 8)
- Newburgh & South Shore (Box 170, Folder 9)
- North Pacific (Box 170, Folder 10)
- Pacific Electric RR Co. (Box 170, Folder 11)
- Pennsy. RR Co. (Box 170, Folder 12)
- Peoria. Pekin (Box 170, Folder 13)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie (Box 170, Folder 14)
- Reading Co. (Box 170, Folder 15)
- Safeway Trails (Box 170, Folder 16)
- St. Louis & San Francisco (Box 170, Folder 17)
- San Antonio & Arkansas Pass (Box 170, Folder 18)
- Santa Fe Trail Transp. Co. (Box 170, Folder 19)
- South Buffalo Ry. (Box 170, Folder 20)
- Southern Calif. Rapid Transit (Box 170, Folder 21)
- Southern Pacific Lines (Box 170, Folder 22)
- Spokane, Portland & Seattle (Box 170, Folder 23)
- Staten Island Rapid Transit (Box 170, Folder 24)
- Tennessee Central (Box 170, Folder 25)
- Terminal RR Assn. Of St. Louis (Box 170, Folder 26)
- Texas & New Orleans RR (Box 170, Folder 27)
- Texas & Pacific (Box 170, Folder 28)
- Trinity & Brazos Valley (Box 170, Folder 29)
- Union Pacific (Box 170, Folder 30)
- Union Terminal (Box 170, Folder 31)
- Western Pacific (Box 170, Folder 32)
- Youngstown & Northern RR (Box 170, Folder 33)
- General Managers' Association of Chicago (Box 170, Folder 34)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Text of Case 3522 (Box 171, Folder 1)
- P.S.F. Cases: BRT v. N.Y.C. L-W N.R.A.B - Re: Overtime, 1961 (Box 171, Folder 2)
- P.S.F. Cases: BRT v. NYC RR. Dispute Involving C.U.T. Yardmen, 1953-1961 (Box 171, Folder 3)
- P.S.F. Cases: Canadian Pacific Ry. Co. and BLE, 1961 (Box 171, Folder 4)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Brief Covering Item 3 (Box 171, Folder 5)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Appeal on Item 4 (Box 171, Folder 6)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Appeal for Rehearing, 1962 (Box 171, Folder 7)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Oral Testimony Rehearing Case 3522 (Box 171, Folder 8)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Bd. Of Appeals #13744, Northern District Lodge #1012 (Box 171, Folder 9)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Contents from BRT Attys. Yard Assignments, etc. (Box 171, Folder 10)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Oral Testimonies, 1958 (Box 171, Folder 11)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Appeal of Gen'l Chairman NCY-LW from BRT Recommendations (Box 171, Folder 12)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Appeal and Oral Testimonies (Box 171, Folder 13)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Rehearing & Oral Testimony (Box 171, Folder 14)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Related Information & Case Brief, 1958 (Box 171, Folder 15)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Contents from BRT Attys. Exhibits of Various Points Used In Trial, etc., 1964 (Box 171, Folder 16)
  February 1964
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Rebuttal to Northern Districts Submission, 1960 (Box 171, Folder 17)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Contents from BRT Attys. Work Assignments, 1940-1962 (Box 171, Folder 18)
- Cases: Aliquippa & Southern RR Co., 1948 (Box 171, Folder 19)
- Cases: Monongahela RR Co., 1949 (Box 171, Folder 20)
- Erie RR. Board of Adjustments, 1953 (Box 171, Folder 21)
- Cases: NRAB Chicago Great Western RR Co., 1936 (Box 171, Folder 22)
- Cases: NRAB Chicago, Rock Island, Pacific Ry. - Chicago, Rock Island, Gulf Ry., 1936 (Box 171, Folder 23)
- Cases: Baltimore & Ohio RR Vacation Agreement Dispute, 1958 (Box 171, Folder 24)
- Cases: (NMB) Atlantic Coast Line RR, 1960 (Box 171, Folder 25)
- Cases: NRAB Detroit Terminal RR Co., 1939 (Box 171, Folder 26)
- Cases: (NRAB) Detroit Terminal RR, 1934 (Box 171, Folder 27)
- Cases: D&RGW RR, 1951 (Box 171, Folder 28)
- Cases: NRAB Chicago Gr. Western RR Co., 1936 (Box 171, Folder 29)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - W. P. Kennedy File, 1960-1962 (Box 172, Folder 1)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Exhibits on Behalf of BRT File A, 1958-1962 (Box 172, Folder 2)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Exhibits on Behalf of BRT File B, 1962 (Box 172, Folder 3)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - File of W. P. Kennedy (Box 172, Folder 4)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Dispute Dealing with Item 1 (Box 172, Folder 5)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Dispute Before Bd. Of Appeals Dealing with Item 2 (Box 172, Folder 6)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - W.D. Submission to Bd. Of Appeals (Box 172, Folder 7)
- P.S.F. Cases: Niles-Elkhart Dispute - Western Division Submission to Pres. Comm. (Box 172, Folder 8)
- Cases: Bd. Of Appeals - re: Niles-Elkhart, 1960 (Box 172, Folder 9)
- Cases: NYC-W. Dist. Committee Copy of Brief Submitted (Box 172, Folder 10)
- File 13744 - Bd. Of A. Case 3522 Brief (Box 172, Folder 11)
- Cases: West District's Brief - re: Niles-Elkhart (Box 173, Folder 1)
- Cases: re Misc. - Whitney's file of cases before N.RR.A.Bd. (Box 173, Folder 2)
- An Examination into Awards - First Division - National Railroad Adjustment Board (Box 173, Folder 3)
- NRAB Miscellaneous File, 1934-1940 (Box 173, Folder 4)
- NRAB BRT - NYC Award #4932, 1940 (Box 173, Folder 5)
- NRAB re: Fiscal Policy, 1958-1960 (Box 173, Folder 6)
- NRAB re: Third Party Notice, 1959-1962 (Box 173, Folder 7)
- NRAB re: Joint Letter Situation Confronting NRAB 1st Division, 1949 (Box 173, Folder 8)
- NRAB, 1934-1939 (Box 174, Folder 1)
- NRAB, 1938-1940 (Box 174, Folder 2)
- NRAB, 1940 (Box 174, Folder 3)
- NRAB, 1940-1942 (Box 174, Folder 4)
- NRAB, 1945 (Box 174, Folder 5)
- NRAB, 1955-1957 (Box 174, Folder 6)
- NRAB File used by A. Whitney testimony before the special on labor, 1946 (Box 175, Folder 1)
- NRAB re: Handling of Grievances, 1945 (Box 175, Folder 2)
- NRAB B&O RR Creation of 3-man board for purpose of disposing of cases before NRAB, 1943 (Box 175, Folder 3)
- NRAB File used by J. R. Harvey at Chicago, Illinois, 1945 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  October 20, 1945
- NRAB 1st Division, 1937 (Box 175, Folder 5)
- NRAB 3rd Division, 1962 (Box 175, Folder 6)
- NRAB 3rd Division, 1934-1948 (Box 175, Folder 7)
- NRAB 1st Division Request for Referee, 1948-1955 (Box 175, Folder 8)
- NRAB 1st Division, 1956-1959 (Box 175, Folder 9)
- NRAB 1st Division Re: Circular letter, Index to Awards 11501-15500, 1952 (Box 175, Folder 10)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1952-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1948-1954 (Box 176, Folder 2)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1947-1952 (Box 176, Folder 3)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1950-1954 (Box 176, Folder 4)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 5)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1953 (Box 176, Folder 6)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1953 (Box 176, Folder 7)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1953 (Box 176, Folder 8)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1947-1949 (Box 176, Folder 9)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1951-1953 (Box 176, Folder 10)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1949-1951 (Box 176, Folder 11)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1942-1948 (Box 176, Folder 12)
- PSF NRAB Administrative Correspondence, 1941 (Box 176, Folder 13)
- PSF NRAB Awards/Cases Pertaining to Issue of "Drunken RR Driving" folder 1, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 14)
- PSF NRAB Awards/Cases Pertaining to Issue of "Drunken RR Driving" folder 2, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 15)
- PSF NRAB First Division Cases, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 16)
  June - December 1946
- PSF NRAB 1st Division Cases, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 17)
- PSF NRAB First Division, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 18)
- PSF NRAB1st Division, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 19)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1946 (Box 176, Folder 20)
- PSF NRAB Cases Pending/Awards Rendered, 1947-1948 (Box 176, Folder 21)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1940-1942 (Box 176, Folder 22)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1940 (Box 176, Folder 23)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1939-1940 (Box 176, Folder 24)
- PSF NRAB General Index, 1942 (Box 176, Folder 25)
- PSF NRAB Misc. Cases, 1950-1957 (Box 176, Folder 26)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1947 (Box 176, Folder 27)
- PSF NRAB 1st Division, 1950-1952 (Box 176, Folder 28)
- PSF NRAB re: Discontinuance of Penn RR Engine & Train Service System Bd. Of Adjustment, 1939-1940 (Box 177, Folder 1)
- PSF NRAB re: Discontinuance of Penn RR Engine & Train Service System Bd. Of Adjustment, 1934-1937 (Box 177, Folder 2)
- PSF NRAB re: Discontinuance of Penn RR Engine & Train Service System Bd. Of Adjustment, 1934-1937 (Box 177, Folder 3)
- PSF NRAB re: BRT/Various RR Co., 1950-1960 (Box 177, Folder 4)
- PSF NRAB re: BRT/Various RR Parties to Disputes, 1960 (Box 177, Folder 5)
- PSF NRAB re: BRT/Various RR Parties to Disputes, 1960 (Box 177, Folder 6)
- PSF NRAB General Information, 1934-1935 (Box 177, Folder 7)
- PSF NRAB Penn RR Dispute, 1936 (Box 177, Folder 8)
- PSF NRAB re: ORT Complaint, 1935 (Box 177, Folder 9)
- NRAB - General File, 1942-1943 (Box 177, Folder 10)
- NRAB General File (Box 177, Folder 11)
- PSF NRAB Cases Pending 1st Division, 1949 (Box 177, Folder 12)
- PSF NRAB Cases Pending 1st Division, 1949 (Box 177, Folder 13)
- PSF NRAB First Division, 1947-1948 (Box 177, Folder 14)
- PSF NRAB Florida East Coast Ry., 1936 (Box 177, Folder 15)
- PSF NRAB Application of Award 139 Chicago, Burlington & Quincy RR, 1935 (Box 177, Folder 16)
- PSF NRAB Chicago, Texas & Pacific Ry., 1936 (Box 177, Folder 17)
- PSF NRAB Supplemental Boards, 1953 (Box 177, Folder 18)
- PSF NRAB: NRAB/RLEA, 1935-1936 (Box 177, Folder 19)
- Cases: So. Ry. Co., Georgia Southern & Florida Ry. Co., 1968 (Box 178, Folder 1)
- Cases: So. Pacific Lines, 1937 (Box 178, Folder 2)
- Cases: Oregon & Northwestern RR., 1940 (Box 178, Folder 3)
- Cases: Terminal RR Assoc. of St. Louis, 1947 (Box 178, Folder 4)
- Cases: (WMB) Spokane, Portland, Seattle Ry. Co., 1954-1957 (Box 178, Folder 5)
- PSF Cases: Thomas v. BRT Exhibits I, II (Box 178, Folder 6)
- PSF Cases: Thomas v. BRT Exhibits 3-6 (Box 178, Folder 7)
- PSF Cases: Thomas v. BRT Exhibits 9-12 (Box 178, Folder 8)
- PSF Cases: Thomas v. BRT Exhibits 13-14 (Box 178, Folder 9)
- PSF Cases: Thomas v. BRT Exhibits 16-18 (Box 178, Folder 10)
- PSF Cases: Thomas v. BRT Exhibits 19-26 (Box 178, Folder 11)
- Cases: Western Maryland Ry. Co., 1952 (Box 178, Folder 12)
- PSF Cases: Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Co. v. BRT Special Bd. Of Adjustment No.47, 1954 (Box 178, Folder 13)
  September 2-17, 1954
- PSF Representation Disputes re: Nat'l Mediation Bd. Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 178, Folder 14)
- PSF Representation Disputes re: Nat'l Mediation Bd. Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 178, Folder 15)
- PSF Representation Disputes re: Nat'l Mediation Bd. Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 178, Folder 16)
- PSF Nat'l RR Adjustment Bd. re: Regional Bds. Appointees, 1934 (Box 178, Folder 17)
- PSF Represent. Disputes: NYC/Ohio Central RR., 1955-1960 (Box 178, Folder 18)
- PSF Representation Disputes re: Jurisdiction of Several Government Agencies, 1943 (Box 178, Folder 19)
- PSF Representation Disputes: Nat'l Mediation Board Intervention (US Bd. Of Mediation), 1940-1949 (Box 178, Folder 20)
- PSF Representation Disputes: US Bd. Of Mediation, 1940-1949 (Box 178, Folder 21)
- PSF Representation Disputes re: Nat'l Mediation Bd., 1943-1949 (Box 178, Folder 22)
- PSF Representation Disputes: Nat'l Mediation Bd. (US Bd. Of Mediation), 1945-1947 (Box 178, Folder 23)
- Representation Disputes re: Nat'l Mediation Bd. Corres. & Cases, 1950-1959 (Box 179, Folder 1)
- Representation Disputes re: Nat'l Mediation Bd. Corres. & Cases, 1960-1962 (Box 179, Folder 2)
- Representation Disputes: Canadian Nat'l Ry. v. BLE, 1961 (Box 179, Folder 3)
- Repres. Disputes: Des Moines Union Ry. Co. BRT/SUNA, 1967 (Box 179, Folder 4)
- Represent. Disputes re: Kansas City Terminal Dispute BRT/SUNA, 1948 (Box 179, Folder 5)
- Rep. Disputes: Merger SUNA/BRT, 1958 (Box 179, Folder 6)
- Prop. BRT-ORC&B Representation Election Frisco RR (Box 179, Folder 7)
- Rep. Disputes: BRT - Propaganda re: Corr. w/ ORC&B Rules Case, 1964 (Box 179, Folder 8)
- Rep. Disputes: Conducting Rep. Elections BRT/ORC&B Corr., 1962 (Box 179, Folder 9)
- Rep. Disputes: BRT/ORC/Order of Sleeping Car Conductors, 1942 (Box 179, Folder 10)
- Rep. Disputes: BRT Merger or Fight Edict, 1964 (Box 179, Folder 11)
- Rep. Disputes: Misc. Info (Box 179, Folder 12)
- Rep. Disputes: SUNA v. BRT Opposition to BRT Affiliation with AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 179, Folder 13)
- Rep. Disputes: BRT/SUNA NYC R, 1932-1934 (Box 179, Folder 14)
- Rep. Disputes: No. Pacific RR SUNA-BRT (Box 179, Folder 15)
- Rep. Disputes: B&O RR BRT vs. SUNA (Box 179, Folder 16)
- Rep. Disputes: BLE/BRT, 1943 (Box 179, Folder 17)
- Rep. Disputes: ORC v. NMB & BRT District Court Case (Box 179, Folder 18)
- Rep. Disputes: BRT/SUNA Michigan Central RR and Misc. Inter-Union Relations, 1926-1943 (Box 179, Folder 19)
- Repres. Disputes: Ray v. BRT (SUNA v. BRT), 1935 (Box 179, Folder 20)
- Rep. Disputes: NMB - BRT v. O.R.C., 1944 (Box 179, Folder 21)
- Rep. Disputes: Reed Georgia Case - District Terminal RR Co. v. SUNA, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 22)
- Rep. Disputes: SUNA & Other Brotherhoods, 1932-1934 (Box 179, Folder 23)
- 1951 (Box 180, Folder 1)
- Wages - Rules - USA, 1952 (Box 180, Folder 2)
- 1952 (USA) (Box 180, Folder 3)
- 1952 (Box 180, Folder 4)
- 1954 (Box 180, Folder 5)
- 1956 (Box 180, Folder 6)
- 1956 (US) (Box 180, Folder 7)
- BRT - Wage Rules Movement - Carriers Exhibits, 1956 (Box 180, Folder 8)
- Wage Rules - Employees Exhibits, 1956 (Box 180, Folder 9)
- 1956 (US) (Box 180, Folder 10)
- Misc. (Box 180, Folder 11)
- Employees' Exhibit No. 6: Before the Emergency Board (Box 180, Folder 12)
- Meeting of Disputes Committee, 1954 (Box 180, Folder 13)
- U. S. Wage-Rules Movements, 1954-1955 (Box 180, Folder 14)
- Rules CF (Box 180, Folder 15)
- 1955 (USA) (Box 180, Folder 16)
- Info re. 5 Day Work Wk. in US (Box 180, Folder 17)
- 1953 (USA) (Box 180, Folder 18)
- 1964 (Box 180, Folder 19)
- Employees' Exhibits (Box 181, Folder 1)
- BRT - Wage Rules Movement - Carriers Exhibits, etc., 1956 (Box 181, Folder 2)
- Rules Cases - The Operating Employees Rules Case, 1946 (Box 181, Folder 3)
- 1956 (US) (Box 181, Folder 4)
- 1957 (US) (Box 181, Folder 5)
- 1956 (USA) (Box 181, Folder 6)
- 1953-57 (US), 1953-1957 (Box 181, Folder 7)
- Rules Cases, 1946 (Box 182, Folder 1)
- The Operating Employees Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit D (Box 182, Folder 2)
- Article XIV (Box 182, Folder 3)
- Exhibit No. 25: Wage, Operating and Financial Statistics of Short Lines Railroads (Box 182, Folder 4)
- The Dining Car Stewards Case: Carriers' Exhibit 16 (Box 182, Folder 5)
- The Operating Employees Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 9 (Box 182, Folder 6)
- The Dining Car Stewards Case: Carriers' Exhibit B (Box 182, Folder 7)
- The Operating Employees Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 42 (Box 182, Folder 8)
- Decisions of Committee, 1953 (Box 182, Folder 9)
- Statistics - Yearbook of Information US, 1959 (Box 182, Folder 10)
- Unemployment Benefits - Train & Engine Service (Box 182, Folder 11)
- 1959 USA (Box 182, Folder 12)
- 1961 (Box 182, Folder 13)
- 1961 (US) (Box 182, Folder 14)
- US Wage Movement, 1959 (Box 182, Folder 15)
- US Wage Movement (Steel Railroads), 1959 (Box 182, Folder 16)
- Carriers' Exhibit No. W-13: Reports of Fact Finding Boards (Box 182, Folder 17)
- Wartime Wages and Railroad Labor (Box 182, Folder 18)
- BRT Misc. (Box 182, Folder 19)
- Agreements - Providing Specific Payments when Trainmen and Yardmen are Required to Couple and Uncouple Hose (Box 182, Folder 20)
- 1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
- 1952 (Box 183, Folder 2)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit A (Box 183, Folder 3)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit C (Box 183, Folder 4)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit D (Box 183, Folder 5)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 13 (Box 183, Folder 6)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 14 (Box 183, Folder 7)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 15 (Box 183, Folder 8)
- Conductors & Trainmen 40-Hour Week & Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit 18 (Box 183, Folder 9)